hackmytrip.com 2017-01-28

# Privacy Policy - Travel Codex

We are committed to protecting your privacy through our compliance with this “Privacy Policy.” For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the terms “we,” “us,” or “our” mean Travel Codex, LLC. The term “web site” means this web site — travelcodex.com — and portions of other web pages and web content through which you have accessed this Privacy Policy.

Travel Codex does not automatically collect or store any personal identifying information about visitors to this web site. Travel Codex does automatically collect and store other data including:

  * Internet protocol (IP) addresses
  * Platform type ( _e.g._ , Windows)
  * Browser type
  * Internet service providers
  * Referring/exit pages
  * Number of clicks
  * Date/time stamps

Third-party companies (such as Google AdSense) use cookies to display advertising information when visiting this web site. These cookies may be used by these third-party companies and their partners to effectively target their advertisements to target audiences. You can learn more about how advertisements are displayed and cookies are stored as well as your ability to opt out of such features by visiting [Google’s website on Advertising Privacy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

### Sale of Information

Travel Codex does not sell or share any personal information without your permission. Please note that we have financial relationships with some of the merchants mentioned here. We may be compensated if consumers choose to utilize the links located throughout the content on this site and generate sales for said merchant.

When entering contests, giveaways, or other promotions, readers may be requested to use services provided by a third party to record entrants, verify certain actions (like agreeing to follow someone on Twitter), and select and contact the winner. Readers are required to supply a personal email address if they choose to enter so that they may be contacted in the event they win a prize. These email addresses are not used for any other purpose. Readers will be alerted at the time of entry if asked to supply additional personal information.

### Mailing Lists and Social Media

Travel Codex encourages readers to subscribe to daily or weekly email newsletters and to follow Travel Codex and its contributors through social media services such as Twitter, Facebook, etc. These alternate contact methods may provide the opportunity to receive additional content as well as additional advertising and marketing materials not found on the web site. The decision to subscribe, follow, or like Travel Codex or a contributor is entirely optional, and readers may opt out at any time. For assistance, please email [scott@travelcodex.com](mailto:scott@travelcodex.com).

Lists of email addresses, Twitter followers, _etc._ are never sold to or shared with third parties without your permission. However, subscribers may be contacted about other offers provided by Travel Codex, LLC.

### Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

### Affiliate Marketing

**Disclaimer: This content is not provided or commissioned by the credit card issuer. Opinions expressed here are author’s alone, not those of the credit card issuer, and have not been reviewed, approved or otherwise endorsed by the credit card issuer. This site may be compensated through the credit card issuer Affiliate Program.**

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Travel Codex continues to add, remove, and develop new ways to ways to improve the services and features provided. As such, this policy is subject to change. The current Privacy Policy will be available in this section of the web site.

Any questions, comments, or concerns can be addressed by email to [scott@travelcodex.com](mailto:scott@travelcodex.com).
